<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="main_title">Tour Guide Version 1.0</string>
    <string name="category_culture">Culture</string>
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_monuments">Monuments</string>
    <string name="category_shopping">Shopping</string>


    <!-- Cultural places names -->
    <string name="faneuil_hall_in_boston">Faneuil Hall in Boston</string>
    <string name="river_walk_in_san_antonio">River Walk in San Antonio</string>
    <string name="white_house_in_washington">White House in Washington</string>
    <string name="walt_disney_world_in_orlando">Walt Disney World in Orlando</string>
    <string name="french_quarter_in_new_orleans">French Quarter in New Orleans</string>

    <!-- Cultural places Descriptions -->
    <string name="faneuil_hall_in_boston_description">One of the most historic destinations in Boston, a city already
        full of heritage, is Faneuil Hall Marketplace. Also known as the Cradle of Liberty, this early 18th century
        structure served as a space where early leaders gathered to fight against oppression in the years before and
        during the American Revolutionary War. Today, touring Faneuil Hall Marketplace means lots of opportunity to
        shop for local produce and desserts in the indoor and outdoor marketplace.</string>

    <string name="river_walk_in_san_antonio_description">In the city of San Antonio, Texas, there are few attractions more
        ppealing than the River Walk. Also known as the Paseo del Rio, the River Walk is a network of walkways lining the
        San Antonio River. Reserved for pedestrians, the revitalized area is packed with fascinating architecture,
        lush greenery and water views. The River Walk is a hub for dining and culinary exploration in this Texan city.
        It is possible to dig into Tex-Mex cuisine, upscale French fare and everything in between in this one easily
        navigable destination.</string>

    <string name="white_house_in_washington_description">The White House in Washington DC is the official residence and
        office of the President of the United States. It was built between 1792 and 1800 and first used by President John Adams.
        After the 9/11 attacks it has become more difficult to visit the White House and today tours are available only
        for groups of 10 or more and must be requested up to six months in advance through your member of Congress or
        your country’s US Ambassador.</string>

    <string name="walt_disney_world_in_orlando_description">Orlando, Florida, is a hub of amusement parks,
        but none is so popular as Walt Disney World. Many travelers don’t realize that Walt Disney World is actually
        made up of several distinct theme parks, including the Magic Kingdom, Epcot, Hollywood Studios,
        Animal Kingdom and the Blizzard Beach Water Park. Visitors will be able to enjoy thrill rides,
        watch Broadway-quality shows and explore the nightlife, cuisine, shopping and entertainment at Disney Springs.</string>


    <string name="french_quarter_in_new_orleans_description">New Orleans, Louisiana, is made up of several unique districts,
        but none is so famous as the French Quarter. Also known as the Vieux Carre, the French Quarter truly explores the rich
        French colonial influences on the city of New Orleans. Incredible architecture abounds, with the St. Louis Cathedral
        being the main attraction. The French Quarter boasts the Moon Walk, a paved walkway next to the Mississippi River, as
        well as Bourbon Street, the undeniable hub of nightlife, drinking and entertainment in the city.</string>

    <!-- Cultural places LocationCoordinates -->
    <string name="faneuil_hall_in_boston_location">lat:42.3602542,long:-71.0569365</string>
    <string name="river_walk_in_san_antonio_location">lat:29.4247976,long:-98.4906843</string>
    <string name="white_house_in_washington_location">lat:38.8976805,long:-77.0387238,17</string>
    <string name="walt_disney_world_in_orlando_location">lat:28.3852377,long:-81.5660681</string>
    <string name="french_quarter_in_new_orleans_location">lat:29.9576213,long:-90.0731793</string>


    <!-- Parks names -->
    <string name="mesa_verde">Mesa Verde</string>
    <string name="navy_pier_in_chicago">Navy Pier in Chicago</string>
    <string name="great_smoky_mountains_national_park">Great Smoky Mountains National Park</string>
    <string name="bryce_canyon_national_park">Bryce Canyon National Park</string>
    <string name="sedona_red_rock_country">Sedona Red Rock Country</string>

    <!-- Parks Descriptions -->
    <string name="mesa_verde_description">The Mesa Verde National Park in Colorado is home
        to the preserved homes of the Ancestral Pueblo people. Many of these homes,
        which are carved right from caves and rock faces, date back to the early 13th century.
        Today, it is possible to walk beneath the overhanging cliffs and tour these ancient abodes.
        The Balcony House is especially well preserved, and it boasts 40 rooms that are accessible
        exclusively by ladder. The nearby Cliff Palace is even bigger, and it is believed to have
        housed more than 100 people in its 150 original rooms.</string>

    <string name="navy_pier_in_chicago_description">Extending over the waters of Lake Michigan is Navy Pier,
        an enormous pier in the heart of Chicago’s coastal Streeterville neighborhood. Within the pier,
        there are countless attractions suited to the whole family. Beautifully manicured gardens are the ideal
        place for a scenic stroll, and lots of souvenir shops are a wonderful way to snag gifts on a vacation
        to Chicago. The pier is also home to the Chicago Children’s Museum, two theaters and an abundance of
        excellent restaurants.</string>

    <string name="great_smoky_mountains_national_park_description">Straddling the border between Tennessee and North
        Carolina is the Great Smoky Mountains National Park. The park is the most visited in the entire country,
        thanks in large part to its enormous size and its incredible scenery. Visitors can hike through old growth
        forest, spot hundreds of species of birds and check out the two visitor centers. Hikes can also wind through
        trails that lead to the waterfalls of Laurel Falls and the vistas of Clingman’s Dome.</string>

    <string name="bryce_canyon_national_park_description">Located in Southern Utah, Bryce Canyon National Park is a breathtaking
        display of rock formations. Technically, Bryce Canyon isn’t a canyon, but a series of natural amphitheaters.
        Mormon settlers once called the canyon home, but now most visitors come for the awe-inspiring views and the
        magnificent hiking opportunities. Sunset Point is one of the most popular vantage points, offering panoramic views of the red,
        yellow and orange rock formations. Queen’s Garden Trail is another favorite, because it offers green trees amongst the red
        rocks for a brilliant juxtaposition.</string>

    <string name="sedona_red_rock_country_description">A two-hour drive north of Phoenix is Sedona, Arizona. Sedona isn’t a big city,
        but it is a major tourist attraction in the USA thanks to its gorgeous red rock landscape. Known as Red Rock Country,
        this region is an outdoor lover’s dream. Countless canyons, creeks and paths encourage outdoor activity, with Cathedral
        Rock Trail being one of the local favorite hiking spots. One of the most interesting spots in Sedona combines the new with
        the old, with the contemporary Chapel of the Holy Cross built right into the side of the red rocks themselves.</string>

    <!-- Parks Locations -->
    <string name="mesa_verde_location">lat:37.2429765,long:-108.5356693</string>
    <string name="navy_pier_in_chicago_location">lat:41.8923282,long:-87.6142967</string>
    <string name="great_smoky_mountains_national_park_location">lat:35.6070357,long:-83.8144551</string>
    <string name="bryce_canyon_national_park_location">lat:37.5735687,long:-112.3187443</string>
    <string name="sedona_red_rock_country_location">lat:34.8686369,long:-111.7639592</string>


    <!-- Monuments names -->
    <string name="mount_rushmore">Mount Rushmore</string>
    <string name="national_world_war_ii_Memorial">National World War II Memorial</string>
    <string name="castle_clinton_national_park">Castle Clinton National Park</string>
    <string name="lincoln_memorial">Lincoln Memorial</string>
    <string name="george_washington_memorial_parkway">George Washington Memorial Parkway</string>

    <!-- Monuments Descriptions -->
    <string name="mount_rushmore_description">Perhaps the most unmistakably American landmark is Mount Rushmore,
        a national memorial located in South Dakota. Constructed in the early 20th century, Mount Rushmore depicts
        the faces of four former American presidents, each of which is carved and blasted from the side of a rock face.
        Visitors can admire the larger-than-life faces of Thomas Jefferson, George Washington,
        Abraham Lincoln and Theodore Roosevelt. The short Presidential Trail
        at the base of Mount Rushmore provides better views and an interesting perspective on the landmark.</string>

    <string name="national_world_war_ii_Memorial_description">Little over a decade old, Washington D.C.’s World War II Memorial
        has quickly become a must-visit spot for anyone visiting the nation’s capital. Made up of 56 pillars, a fountain and two
        arches, it is a simple but striking tribute to the sacrifices made during WW2.</string>

    <string name="castle_clinton_national_park_description">Originally built in 1812 to stop a British Invasion, Castle Clinton
        marks the beginning of the development of New York City. It has been a fort, a theatre, an immigration station,
        and now it is an essential tourist attraction for all Manhattan visitors.</string>

    <string name="lincoln_memorial_description">The ubiquitous Lincoln Memorial still manages to be awe-inspiring even after
        you have seen it on countless postcards and everywhere from textbooks to an episode of ‘The Simpsons’.
        The giant statue surrounded by the words of the Gettysburg Address is a must-visit for any American wanting
        to pay tribute to a great president.</string>

    <string name="george_washington_memorial_parkway_description">One of the USA’s so-called ‘All American Roads’, the George Washington
        Memorial Parkway is a 25-mile road through Virginia (with a small segment in D.C.) full of memorials and reminders of America’s
        history as a nation, from the Marine Corps War Memorial to the Arlington Bridge into Washington.</string>

    <!-- Monuments Locations -->
    <string name="mount_rushmore_location">lat:43.8791063,long:-103.4612607</string>
    <string name="national_world_war_ii_Memorial_location">lat:38.8894141,long:-77.0416496</string>
    <string name="castle_clinton_national_park_location">lat:40.7034441,long:-74.0189963</string>
    <string name="lincoln_memorial_location">lat:38.8893093,long:-77.0485429</string>
    <string name="george_washington_memorial_parkway_location">lat:38.8435777,long:-77.0512763</string>

    <!-- Shopping places names -->
    <string name="mall_of_america">Mall of America</string>
    <string name="aventura_mall">Aventura Mall</string>
    <string name="del_amo_fashion_center">Del Amo Fashion Center</string>
    <string name="woodfield_mall">Woodfield Mall</string>
    <string name="sawgrass_mills">Sawgrass Mills</string>

    <string name="mall_of_america_description">The history of modern mall development is divided into two distinct eras:
        everything that came before Mall of America and everything after. With more than 400 shops,
        MOA changed the playing field radically, not just in terms of size (for years it was the world’s
        largest mall) but also that heady blend of retail, entertainment, and “Wow!” factor that subsequent
        malls have tried to achieve. MOA continues to lead them all with 40 million visitors—nearly as many as Italy’s
        foreign tourist arrivals last year. </string>

    <string name="aventura_mall_description">The greater Miami area’s largest mall is an integral part of a super-posh coastal
        enclave that includes the Turnberry Isle resort and championship golf course, Gulfstream Park thoroughbred horse track,
        and the upscale Golden Beach/Golden Isles residential area. Cashing in on south Florida’s tourism bounty, the mall
        organizes shopping experiences for visiting conventions and hosts special events like the Chocolate Festival,
        Great American Bake Sale, Miami’s Most Photogenic Baby contest, and a regular farmers’ market.</string>

    <string name="del_amo_fashion_center_description">The prototypical L.A. mall, Del Amo has appeared in movies like Valley Girl,
        Bad Santa, and Beverly Hills 90210. It attracts a mixed bag of well-heeled Palos Verdes residents, surfer dudes from nearby
        Redondo Beach, and inner-city patrons from Compton and Long Beach. Del Amo’s most popular entertainment attractions
        are an 18-theater Cineplex and a Lucky Strike Lanes bowling alley.</string>

    <string name="woodfield_mall_description">Located just outside of Chicago, Woodfield is the number one tourist destination in the
        State of Illinois. Its name pays posthumous tribute to two of the greatest retailers of all time: General Robert E. Wood of
        Sears fame and the legendary Marshall Field. Many of the specialty stores are the largest of their kind in the U.S.,
        and Woodfield is often used to test new store design and marketing concepts. Its trademark stainless-steel sculptures were
        fashioned by artist Robert Engman.</string>

    <string name="sawgrass_mills_description">Like Del Amo on the left coast, this Florida landmark is one of the anchor properties
        of the Simon Property Group, the nation’s largest mall owner. Sawgrass takes its name from the nearby Everglades,
        located just across the expressway from the mall on the western outskirts of Fort Lauderdale. In addition to
        the core enclosed area, Sawgrass includes an outdoor entertainment area called the Oasis and an outlet component dubbed the Colonnade.
    </string>

    <!-- Shopping places Locations -->
    <string name="mall_of_america_location">lat:44.8548689,long:-93.2444088</string>
    <string name="aventura_mall_location">lat:25.9581989,long:-80.1443127</string>
    <string name="del_amo_fashion_center_location">lat:33.8305609,long:-118.351763</string>
    <string name="woodfield_mall_location">lat:42.0452961,long:-88.0405939</string>
    <string name="sawgrass_mills_location">lat:26.1516459,long:-80.3242469</string>
</resources>
